Guide to the William and James Trahern account books, 1803-1827 RL.11671
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
William and James Trahern account books
1803-1827
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Trahern, William.
RL.11671
12 Volumes
William and James Trahern were merchants in Brunswick (Brunswick Co.), Virginia. Merchants' accounts, including daybooks, 1803-1806, and a record of cotton storage, 1825-1827, of William Trahern; and daybooks, 1806-1822, and an index of James Trahern.
Biographical / Historical
William and James Trahern were merchants in Brunswick (Brunswick Co.), Virginia.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Provenance
The William and James Trahern account books were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a purchase in 1933.
Collection Overview
Merchants' accounts, including daybooks, 1803-1806, and a record of cotton storage, 1825-1827, of William Trahern; and daybooks, 1806-1822, and an index of James Trahern.
Business records -- Virginia -- Brunswick; Cotton -- Storage -- Costs; Merchants -- Accounting; Brunswick County (Va.) -- History; Account books; Trahern, William.; Trahern, James; Trahern, James
- William Trahern, Cotton Storage, 1825-1827 (Volume M-3935)
- William Trahern, Day book, 1803-1806 (Volume F-3936)
- William Trahern, Day book, 1804-1805 (Volume L-3937)
- William Trahern, Day book, 1805 (Volume L-3938)
- William Trahern, Day book, 1805-1806 (Volume L-3939)
- William Trahern, Daby book, 1805-1806 (Volume L-3940)
- James Trahern, Day book, 1806 (Volume L-3941)
- James Trahern, Day book, 1806-1807 (Volume L-3942)
- James Trahern, Day book, 1806-1807 (Volume L-3943)
- James Trahern, Day book, 1806-1817 (Volume L-3944)
- James Trahern and Company, Day book, 1807-1822 (Volume L-3945)
- James Trahern, Index (Volume L-3946)